[{"answer": "We followed the evidence.", "docId": "121204pmt", "aSentId": 38, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 37}, {"answer": "Well, we start talking about the facts, those --", "docId": "121204pmt", "aSentId": 47, "question": "Bill Nye, your response?", "qSentId": 46}, {"answer": "Sure.", "docId": "121204pmt", "aSentId": 54, "question": "Do you agree that when I was a kid or when you were a kid, there was 340 parts per million of carbon dioxide in the atmosphere?", "qSentId": 53}, {"answer": "OK.", "docId": "121204pmt", "aSentId": 57, "question": "What's your point?", "qSentId": 56}, {"answer": "It's human activity.", "docId": "121204pmt", "aSentId": 70, "question": "And what do you put that rate down to, Bill?", "qSentId": 69}, {"answer": "Well, the biggest thing is when I was 9 years old, the earth's population changed from 2.999 billion to three billion.", "docId": "121204pmt", "aSentId": 77, "question": "And what are the biggest factors, the manmade factors creating the acceleration of CO2 in the atmosphere?", "qSentId": 76}, {"answer": "Sure.", "docId": "121204pmt", "aSentId": 98, "question": "How do you explain that the Eastern Seaboard, for example, is getting some of the warmest weather it's ever had at the same time that California has been plunged into storm after storm in the last week and you see New York last month had the worst hurricane it's ever endured and so on and so on?", "qSentId": 97}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "121204pmt", "aSentId": 101, "question": "How do you explain that we're getting so many of these freakish weather patterns if at the same time you've got all this extra CO2 in the atmosphere and all these people now guzzling up power and energy and emitting gases that weren't there before?", "qSentId": 100}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "121204pmt", "aSentId": 103, "question": "Surely that is evidence, isn't it?", "qSentId": 102}, {"answer": "Well, we were honored to be invited.", "docId": "121204pmt", "aSentId": 224, "question": "What was your take on the two meetings?", "qSentId": 223}, {"answer": "Well, that's for the Congress to decide and that's part of the debate.", "docId": "121204pmt", "aSentId": 243, "question": "Don't you feel like you're batting the wrong kind of game here?", "qSentId": 242}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, as you know, there were a number of efforts before the election to get this done and there were major differences between the parties, and those parties became a big part of the conversation during the presidential debate.", "docId": "121204pmt", "aSentId": 284, "question": "Why wasn't this done in the first quarter?", "qSentId": 283}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, I think it took the very tough two closings of the federal government, one for six days, the other for 21 days, in order to get to a point where we were able to negotiate seriously to get welfare reform, which was vetoed twice and then signed, and then to get four consecutive balanced budgets, which was a pretty substantial accomplishment, the only time in your lifetime we've had four consecutive American balanced budgets.", "docId": "121204pmt", "aSentId": 343, "question": "What is the way through this and how is this likely, in your expert opinion, to be resolved?", "qSentId": 342}, {"answer": "Well, Piers, I'm happy for you to pay it, too.", "docId": "121204pmt", "aSentId": 368, "question": "Are you?", "qSentId": 367}, {"answer": "Of course I'm prepared.", "docId": "121204pmt", "aSentId": 375, "question": "Would you be happy to?", "qSentId": 374}, {"answer": "Feel good.", "docId": "121204pmt", "aSentId": 433, "question": "How does that make you feel?", "qSentId": 432}, {"answer": "A lot of people.", "docId": "121204pmt", "aSentId": 436, "question": "How many people do you meet on a daily basis who go, you are my hero?", "qSentId": 435}, {"answer": "All you try to do is just relax, really.", "docId": "121204pmt", "aSentId": 444, "question": "When you get down on those blocks and you are about to explode, what actually goes through the Golden Bolt's mind?", "qSentId": 443}, {"answer": "Well, it's just hard work.", "docId": "121204pmt", "aSentId": 457, "question": "Not just any old champion, to be a great champion?", "qSentId": 456}, {"answer": "It's everything.", "docId": "121204pmt", "aSentId": 476, "question": "Is it all of it?", "qSentId": 475}, {"answer": "I think it may have something to do with yams.", "docId": "121204pmt", "aSentId": 497, "question": "Is there something in the Jamaican yam?", "qSentId": 496}, {"answer": "For me, Michael Johnson was definitely one.", "docId": "121204pmt", "aSentId": 504, "question": "Sporting heroes?", "qSentId": 503}, {"answer": "Other sports.", "docId": "121204pmt", "aSentId": 511, "question": "What about other sports?", "qSentId": 510}, {"answer": "I can do a little bit.", "docId": "121204pmt", "aSentId": 530, "question": "Can you do the Gangnam?", "qSentId": 529}, {"answer": "I remember at the Olympics --", "docId": "121204pmt", "aSentId": 545, "question": "Your thoughts?", "qSentId": 544}, {"answer": "I remember at the Olympics, the first Olympics in Beijing, I remember when I was going to run the 200 meters.", "docId": "121204pmt", "aSentId": 547, "question": "Coming from him, he hasn't exactly got the most graceful style, has he?", "qSentId": 546}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "121204pmt", "aSentId": 582, "question": "You got no game?", "qSentId": 581}, {"answer": "My one song I always sing is like, \"one love, one heart, let's get together and feel all right.\"", "docId": "121204pmt", "aSentId": 590, "question": "Can you do any Bob Marley for me?", "qSentId": 589}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "121204pmt", "aSentId": 619, "question": "Why would I be bitter about that, you say?", "qSentId": 618}, {"answer": "The line, whatever you call it.", "docId": "121204pmt", "aSentId": 626, "question": "The cue?", "qSentId": 625}, {"answer": "No, I'm single right now.", "docId": "121204pmt", "aSentId": 632, "question": "Is this true?", "qSentId": 631}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121204pmt", "aSentId": 634, "question": "You're single?", "qSentId": 633}, {"answer": "Let's talk Rio.", "docId": "121204pmt", "aSentId": 640, "question": "What can I say man?", "qSentId": 639}, {"answer": "Without a doubt.", "docId": "121204pmt", "aSentId": 642, "question": "Are you going to go for it in Rio?", "qSentId": 641}, {"answer": "Well, I've mentioned this to my coach and I have said it to him.", "docId": "121204pmt", "aSentId": 644, "question": "How many -- as you sit here now, how many do you think you can race in Rio?", "qSentId": 643}, {"answer": "They're light for the size.", "docId": "121204pmt", "aSentId": 656, "question": "These are Puma, right?", "qSentId": 655}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "121204pmt", "aSentId": 659, "question": "You wear these?", "qSentId": 658}, {"answer": "World Juniors 2002.", "docId": "121204pmt", "aSentId": 664, "question": "Usain, there's a question I always ask people, if you had five minutes to live and I had the power to relive a moment for you from your life, what would you choose?", "qSentId": 663}, {"answer": "It was one of my -- it was a life changing experience for me in every sense.", "docId": "121204pmt", "aSentId": 666, "question": "Why that?", "qSentId": 665}, {"answer": "I had a girl friend for seven years.", "docId": "121204pmt", "aSentId": 678, "question": "Once?", "qSentId": 677}, {"answer": "Vice versa.", "docId": "121204pmt", "aSentId": 680, "question": "Did she break your heart?", "qSentId": 679}]